pes-patch.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy - PES Patch

**Privacy Policy for PES-Patch.com**

PES-Patch.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: PES-Patch.com

  * We collect anonymous statistics about your visit, like which of our pages you viewed.
  * Some 3rd parties like Facebook and Twitter may know you visited this website, if you use their services. We can’t control them but we don’t believe this knowledge poses any threat to you.
  * If you sign up with us we take great care to keep your information safe and we’ll never share it with others without your express permission.
  * We never share your data with 3rd parties except to help us deliver our own services.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. This information stays totally private and is not shared with any other company or institution.

We measure visitors to our website using Google Analytics. This records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. All of that information is anonymous – so we don’t know who you are; just that  _somebody  _visited our site.

The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better.

This site contains links to other sites. PES-Patch.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We use outside ads companies to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site.

 **The Use of a Mailing List on PES-Patch.com**

It is possible for a user to add him/herself to the PES-Patch.com Mailing List. Users of this mailing list can add and remove themselves at any time. When a user removes him of herself then no further PES-Patch.com related mail is send to this user.

 **Security for PES-Patch.com**

PES-Patch.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

 **E-Mail Information**

We may send you email notifications regarding your service (such as invoices) or which you have specifically requested (such as newsletters or notifications when a report is completed). You have the ability to opt out of any of this communication at any time. We will  _never  _provide your personal information or email address to any third parties except where they are specifically employed to help deliver our own services, as detailed above.

 **The Use of Cookies on PES-Patch.com**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site.

The Use of  Advertising on PES-Patch.com  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.

 **Important:** All patches on site are created to be used only with a legal copy of the game.  
You agree to use the site only if you own the game.
